In this game, there is only one king.
Killing Salazar is a crime, action, adventure film directed by Keoni Waxman.
An elite team of DEA agents are assigned to protect a dangerous drug lord and
take refuge in a luxury hotel while they await extraction.
They soon find themselves at the center of an ambush as the drug lord's
former associates launch an explosive assault on the hotel.
John Harrison, played by Steven Seagal.
Maj. Tom Jensen, played by Luke Goss.
Bruno Sinclaire, played by Georges St-Pierre.
Gary Dentze, played by Bruce Crawford.
Eric Ramirez, played by Lauro David Chartrand-DelValle.
Skony (Maj. John Skokowski), played by Darren E. Scott.
Cartels, also known as Killing Salazar, is a 2017 action film starring Luke
Goss and directed by Keoni Waxman, also featuring Steven Seagal.
It had a limited theatrical release on July 7, 2017, and was released
on DVD and digital streaming on September 19, 2017.
The film explores themes of ambush, assault, drug lord, luxury hotel, dea.
The tone is intense.